Juan Munoz Computer Science Student

Phone 630-518-5931 Student Email jmunoz13@aurora.edu Personal Email munozjuan12379@gmail.com LinkedIn linkedin.com/juanmunoz12379

Current student completing Senior year of computer science major. 5 years of work experience, including management and lead roles. I can implement work and leadership qualities I have learned from my previous jobs, into my field of study. My biggest strengths include being teamoriented, having a great work ethic, and the desire to learn.

Work Experience

Hollister Co. / Lead Sales Associate: March 2018 – January 2019

- Began as regular associate and moved way up to a lead position
- Customer oriented tasks
- Learned how to do my individual tasks in order to help the entire team achieve their goal

Express Inc. / Lead Operations: February 2019 - November 2020

- In charge of all operational tasks of the store
- Had to manage small team of 3
- Complete online orders on backroom computers and iPad devices

Pacific Sunwear / Assistant Store Manager: November 2020 – Present

- Manage all opening and closing procedures including sales floor and backroom
- In charge of all associates in the store under me including other managers
- Work with computer systems to keep track of inventory and online sales
- Started as sales associate and worked my way up to high management position

Education

High School Degree, Waubonsie Valley High School: August 2015 – May 2019

- 3.4 GPA
- Honor Roll Junior and Senior Year
- Participated in AP courses and Accelerated Math

Associate in Arts, Waubonsee Community College: August 2019 – December 2021

- 3.6 GPA
- Completed several CS related courses
- Learned Python and Java coding

Major in Computer Science, Aurora University: January 2022 – Present

- 3.4 GPA
- Focus on Software Engineering

Skills

- Able to work in a team as both a member and as a leader
- Knowledge in multiple programming languages including Python and JavaScript
- Knowledge in computer components, specifically PC hardware and software
- Great at learning and taking in information, as well as critical feedback
- Described as positive, determined, and organized